Guide to the Donald E. Knuth papers SC0097
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Computers and Typesetting, Series 2
  The manuscripts were written by Knuth as these systems were being created, together with intermediate versions and log books that show how things developed and changed over the years. Critical comments by leading experts, who helped to refine the ideas, are included. Many of the "first" editions printed by these new methods, at stanford and at many other places around the world, are also preserved here. The period 1977 - 1986 was one of dramatic change in the world of book publishing; numerous keepsakes and specimens from TeX and other systems have been collected.
  - Legal size documents
    - log book and test program for debugging TeX78 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - The first pages of output by TeX, Mar--Jul 1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript of first TeX Manual, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript of first METAFONT Manual, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - original (inco:rrplete) draft of TeX82, Aug--Sep 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Pencil draft of WEB, Sep--oct 1981 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - First use of WEB with TeX82 before it was complete (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Manuscript of TeX82 program, Jan--Jun 1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Log of the first bugs fround in TeX82, Jul--Sep 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Original manuscript of the TeXBook, Oct 1982--Sep 1983 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Manuscript of the PROFILE program, Oct 1983 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Dcx::xnnentation of system used at Universities Press, Belfast, in, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - CTI Math System (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Volume A, The TeXbook
    - First TeX manual: draft copy for making the index, Jul 31 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - First TeX manual: as it was stored in the computer, Aug 27 1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - First TeX manual, Sep 1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - The TeXbook: first printed drafts (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - The TeXbook: second printed drafts (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - The TeXbook: third printed drafts (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - The TeXbook: one-of-a-kind edition used to make the index (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Experiments with TeX done while writing the TeXbook (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - The TeXbook illustrations by Duane Bibby (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - The TeXbook: comments from readers of pre-publication drafts (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - The TeXbook: as marked by Addison-Wesley copy editor (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The TeXbook: book and cover design (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - The TeXbook: Permission letters (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - TeX milieu
    - BBR System, world's first computer controlled printing of text (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Hershey's typographic systems (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - American Math Society research on composition (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - composition systems from commercial vendors (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Typesetting research at universities (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Typesetting research at Bell Laboratories (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Typesetting research at other laboratories (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Fancy word processing with math (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - TeX in the Bay Area (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - TeX elsewhere in the U.S.A. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - TeX in other countries (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Company business re: TeX (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Supplementary work on hyphenation and pagination (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - TeX memorabilia and auxiliary systems
    - The "DOC" system (father of "WEB"), Feb-Mar 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The WEB manual (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - TeXware" " (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Early use of WEB (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Software for the Alphatype CRS (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Samples from first interfaces between TeX or METAFDNT and devices (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Examples of early TeX output: (A) Things I made myself or with Jill (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Examples of early TeX output: (B) Things made by others (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Examples of early TeX output: (C) Books (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, clippings, etc. relevant to TeX (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with American Math Society (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Volume B, TeX: The Program
    - Prototype implementation of TeX, Aug 25 1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Beginnings of first TeX implementation, Oct 14 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - First implementation almost complete, Jan 29 1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - First implementation complete and ready for debugging, 1978 Feb 10 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - After initial debugging, Mar 29 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The first version released" for general use, Aug 2 1978 " (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Fully debugged" version, Aug 1979 " (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - TeX78 as it was in Jul 1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - TeX in Pascal, written by Ignacio Zabala (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - TeX in MESA, written by Leo Guibas, Bob Sedgewick, and Doug Wyatt (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - First draft of TeX82, Sep 6 1981 (incomplete) (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Early draft of TeX82, Jan 2 1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - A more complete draft of TeX82, Mar 28 1982 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - "Nearly complete" draft, Jun 14 1982 " (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - The first complete draft of TeX82, Jun 29 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - TeX82 initial debugging, Jul 13 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Version -0.25" of TeX82, Jul 25 1982 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Version 0 of TeX82, Sep 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Version 0.999 of TeX82, Jul 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Empirical runtime analysis of TeX (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Version 1.0 of TeX82, Dec 3 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Version 1.3 of TeX82, Dec 1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Version 2.0 of TeX82, Nov 11 1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Copy editor's corrections to Volume B, Jan 1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Profiles (timing information) for TeX82, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - TWILL (special variant of WEAVE for Volumes B and (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Volume B, front matter (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - TeXHAX", messages among early users " (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - TUG (TeX Users Group) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - First uses" of TeX, continued " (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Addison-Wesley pUblicity brochures (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Other systems based on TeX (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - TeX addenda; Volume C, The METAFONTbook
    - Miscellaneous correspondence from users (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - A simple system that came before TeX, Jun 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Experiments with the first hyphenation algorithm, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Hyphenation: TeX versus Webster's Collegiate, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - TeX, the name (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Commercial software based on TeX (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Computers and Typesetting: cover designs (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Redesign of METAFONT logo, summer 1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - First draft copies of the METAFONTbook, Chapters 1--13 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - First draft copies of the METAFONTbook, Chapters 14--D (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Readers' comments on METAFONTbook first draft (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Penultimate draft of METAFONTbook (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - METAFONTbook: quotations (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - METAFONTbook: illustrations by Duane Bibby (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - METAFONTbook: illustrations by computer (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - METAFONTbook: copy editor's corrections (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Proto-METAFONT, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Initial design of METAFONT, summer 1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Handwritten code for the first METAFONT (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Complete logs for TeX, METAFONT, Computer Modern (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Knuth, Donald E., The Errors of TEX, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Volume D, METAFONT: The Program
    - First draft of METAFONT interpreter, Dec 15 1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - First draft of METAFONT with raster routines, Jan 1 1979 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - First draft of testable METAFONT system, Apr 15 1979 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - First complete" METAFONT system (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Released" METAFONT (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Tom Spencer's original algorithms for drawing in linear time (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Interim METAFONT manual, used from spring 1984 to fall 1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - State of METAFONT code on Mar 11 1984 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - The first camplete draft of METAFONT84, Mar 18 1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - First working draft of METAFONT84 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - First version of METAFONT to pass the TRAP" test (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Version 0.3 of METAFONT, Sep 27 1984 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Version 0.7 of METAFONT, Jan 17 1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Version 0.95 of METAFONT, Aug 12 1985 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Volume D, continued; METAFONT milieu
    - Version 1.0 of METAFONT, Jan 4 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Profile (running time estimate) of METAFONT, Oct 1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Profile gathering program (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Typography course, spring 1984, with Bigelow and Southall (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Typography course homework: El Palo Alto and border designs (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Typography course homework: Font 1" " (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Equipment brochures, manuals, and samples (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Interfacing METAFONT84 to devices (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Use of my own laser printer! (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - other letterform design systems (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Legibility (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence concerning fonts (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - METAFONT connuentary (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Type specimens (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Volume E, Computer Modern Typefaces
    - What preceded Computer Modern (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Computer Modern, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Computer Modern, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Computer Modern, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Computer Modern published as a Stanford report, Jan 1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Computer Modern, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Computer Modern, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Computer Modern, early 1982 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Major revision of p~r 1982: lowercase letters (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Major revision of Apr 1982: uppercase letters (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Major revision of Apr 1982: numerals (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Major revision of Apr 1982: punctuation and accents (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Major revision of Apr 1982: math symbols (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Computer Modern, summer 1982 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Computer Modern, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Almost Computer Modern Roman, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Almost Computer Modern Italic, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Almost Computer Modern Symbols, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Almost Computer Modern Extensib1es", 1984 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Computer Modern Roman, Jan--Apr 1985 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Volume E, continued; font milieu
    - Computer Modern: final tests, May 1985--Jan 1986 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Christmas card, 1985: Celtic knot font (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript copy for Volume E, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous documents about fonts (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous typographic keepsakes (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Arabic and Hebrew (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Math Symbols (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Chinese and Japanese (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Indian (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Cyrillic (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Work of Nazneen N. Bi11awa1a (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Work of Charles A. Bigelow (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Work of Georgia Tobin (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Work of Rudiger Pfeiffer-Rupp (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Work of Philippe Coueignoux (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous additions
    - The METAFONTbook: original manuscript (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - METAFONT: The Program: original manuscript (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Computer Modern in I new METAFONT I: original manuscript, spring, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Drafts of original TeX implementation (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - The original memo that led to TeX: handwritten draft, May 1977 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Concrete Mathematics, Series 3
  Archives from the development of Concrete Mathematics, a textbook by Ronald L. Graham, Donald E. Knuth and Oren Patashnik. 'This book, published in the surmner of 1988, is based on a Stanford course of the same name that I introduced in 1970 (and it has been taught ever since). It represents sort of a "manifesto" of the way I like to do mathematics, especially the mathematics associated with computer prograrrnning. After nearly twenty years teaching the course, I knew that it was time to put this textbook together and export the ideas to other universities. My goal was to produce the best exposition of mathematical manipulations since, say, cauchy's famous Cours de Mathematigue of the 1820's and 1830's. Ron Graham was a visiting professor who taught the Stanford course twice during my sabbatical leaves, both times with great success. Oren Patashnik was a graduate student in Computer Science who served as teaching assistant in the class several times, under both Graham and me.
  Drafts, proofs, and correspondence pertaining to the textbook by Ronald L. Graham, Donald E. Knuth and Oren Patashnik, which was based on a Stanford course taught by Knuth.
  - Original Drafts
    Patashnik created a draft of the entire book, which was used by Stanford students for two or three years. During the last half of 1987 and the first half of 1988, I rewrote this draft and the result was used as a trial text at Stanford, Princeton, Brown, Columbia, Rice and CUNY. My handwritten manuscripts appear here, together with marked-up copies of Oren's draft, together with high-level notes I made to Graham letting him know the thrust of what I was doing so that he could provide maximum input. Correspondence and preprints of unpublished papers I consul ted during this time are also included.
    This part of the archive consists of ten legal-size folders.
    1.0 Preface, Graffiti and permissions (see below)
    1.1 Chapter One, Recurrent Problems
    1.2 Chapter Two, Sums
    1.3 Chapter Three, Integer Functions
    1.4 Chapter Four, Number Theory
    1.5 Chapter Five, Binomial Coefficients
    1.6 Chapter Six, Special Numbers
    1.7 Chapter Seven, Generating Functions
    1.8 Chapter Eight, Discrete Probability
    1.9 Chapter Nine, Asymptotics
    Each folder has comments written on the outside that were notes to myself about what sources to read as I was writing the material. 'Ihese references are keyed to sixteen years worth of classnotes from the Stanford course; those classnotes are not part of the archive but they do exist in Stanford's Mathematical Sciences Library.
    Our book introduces a novel feature called "graffiti," borrowed from the non-mathematical brochure called Approaching Stanford. We asked stUdents to contribute their own cormnents so that we could print them in the margins of our book. These student contributions are included in folder I.O.
    - Preface, Graffiti, Permission (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Chapter One: Recurrent Problems (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Chapter 'Two: Sums (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Chapter 'Three: Integer Functions (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Chapter Four: Number Theory (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Chapter Five: Binomial Coefficients (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Chapter Six: Special Numbers (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Chapter Seven: Generating Function (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Chapter Eight: Discrete Probability (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Chapter Nine: Asymptotics (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with the publisher
    Here are relevant letters from the production editor and book designer. These are of some interest because we wrote this book at a time when the process of book production is changing dramatically. Instead of sending a manuscript to the publisher and letting them carry the ball, this book was typeset by its authors. Still, we did not want to lose the professional services of a book designer, so we received advice on suitable format before we did the typesetting.
    Our book is interesting from another standpoint because it is the first book to be published with a new family of typefaces designed by Hermann Zapf, especially for mathematics, called AMS Euler. Part of my work on this book, was devoted to fine tuning of these fonts, so that they can be used in other mathematical publications. With the book designers help I was able to create a compatible text face (called Concrete Roman and Italic) to complement Zapf's mathematical characters.
    - Correspondence with Addison-Wesley (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Duplicate and erroneous pages from manuscript (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - First Early Draft
    Here are the pages used by students at Stanford, Princeton, 1987-1988, etc., together with corrections I noted in response to their feedback.
    - Preface, Chapters One, Two and Three (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Chapters Four and Five (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Chapters six and Seven (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Chapters Eight, Nine and Exercises (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Ron Graham's Remarks
    Ron took the responsibility for preparing the index; he marked up a copy of (III) with index terms and made other comments.
    - Preface, Chapters One, Two, Three and Four (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Chapters Five and six (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Chapters Seven, Eight, Nine and Exercises (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Copy editor's Remarks
    Another aspect of typesetting-by-author is shown here. We wanted the help of a professional copy editor as well as a book designer. In this case the copy editor could mark freely anything that needed to be double-checked, knowing that we would ignore all advice that we didn't like. The result, we think, is much better than in previous methods under which the copy editor would have supreme authority but would then be limited to making changes that would not upset the authors when page proofs appeared. This part of the archive also includes some correspondence I had with the copy editor.
    - Correspondence, Style-sheet, Preface, Chapters One and Two (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Chapters Three and Four (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Chapters Five and six (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Chapters Seven and Eight (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Chapter Nine (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Semi-final proofs
    The corrections to (III) based on (IV), (V) and other feedback are shown here in a special format that shows the first raw index we constructed. Final changes and graffiti are written on these laserprinted proofs.
    - Preface, Chapters One and Two (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Chapters Three and Four (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Chapters Five and six (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Chapters Seven, Eight and Nine (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Appendices A: Exercises, B: Bibliography, C: Credits (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Index (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Addenda, 1989-278, Accession ARCH-1989-278
  - Galleys and proofs for The Art of Programming (Box 1)
  - Galleys and proofs for The Art of Programming (Box 2)
  - Galleys and proofs for The Art of Programming (Box 3)
  - Galleys and proofs for The Art of Programming (Box 4)
- Addenda, 1996-147, Accession ARCH-1996-147
  Addendum to the archives of the TeX-METAFONT project drafts, proofs, articles, notes, and other records pertaining to the project, as well as keepsakes and published materials using TeX and/or METAFONT.
  - Galley proofs the second edition of The Art of Computer Programming, Volume 1, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Samples of repro copy used to make Volume 1 with Monotype by Wolf Composition (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Samples of repro copy used to make Surreal Numbers with Monotype by Clowes (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Samples of repro copy used to make volume 2, second edition, with TeX and METAFONT - Knuth's first production output with the Alphatype (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - The WEB system, preliminary pre-release version, November 1981 (one of the first documents of what has become known as Literate Programming) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The GFtoDVI processor: Version 0, April 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The GFtoDVI processor: Version 1.6, September 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Complete listing of TeX with frequency counts of actual usage, 22 October 1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Keepsakes from the early days of TeX: (Box 1, Folder 9)
    System uptime report for the SAIL computer on which Knuth worked The first proofs of proto-Computer Modern type, July 1977; Cover art for the first TeX user manual. American Math Society, 1978; Cover design by Scott Kim for Stanford Computer Forum, using an early draft of the AMS Euler lowercase, Fall 1981; Handouts for TeX mini-courses, Spring 1981; Photo of California vanity plate "DON TEX", n.d.; Formal invitation to TeX's "coming of age" party, December 9, 1983
  - Notes made by Knuth while preparing revision of METAFONT, December 21, 1982 - January 18, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Technical notes related to the inner workings of TeX and METAFONT: (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Computer-aided footwear design by J.R. Manning, December 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - SCRIBE: A document specification language by Brian Reid, October 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Geometric construction of Bernstein poly curves by G.M. Chaikin, Fall 1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Choosing spline directions at knots by John Hobby, Spring 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Choosing velocity parameters for cubic splines by John Hobby, Spring 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correcting outlines for pen width by John Hobby March 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - A Chinese mete-font by John Hobby and Gu Guoan, ICTP83 proceedings, October 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ideas for the new METAFONT by John Hobby, Fall 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - METAFONT programming style by Per Bothner, December 12, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The 6-register method for plotting cubic spines by John Hobby, December 14, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Tension and mock curvature by John Hobby, December 15, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Adjustment to the raster by John Hobby, December 15, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Joints between Bezier curves by Lyle Ramshaw, December 15, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Convolving graph paper tracings by Lyle Ramshaw, December 16, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alternatives to the splines of Manning by John Hobby, December 31, 1983-January 1, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Comments on curves by Leo Guibas and Knuth, January 1, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Reparameterization and other things by Lyle Ramshaw, January 3, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Compromise values of r and s by John Hobby, January 3 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Nifty labeling of Bezier intermediate points by Lyle Ramshaw, February 8, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Proposed raster image processor by Victor Ostromoukhov, Spring 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Adaptation of Liang's hyphenation to Russian by Dimitri Vulis 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Proposed changes to TeX by Jan Rynning, August 16, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ISO standards for extended 8-bit codes, August 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Subtle bugs in METAFONT, October 1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Samples of AMS Euler before re-tuning of Fraktur and script, March 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Demillo and Mathur, Applying grammar-based fault classification to TeX, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Samples of repro copy used to make Computers & Typesetting: (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Volume A - The TeXbook (includes all chapter openers with Duane Bibby art) 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Volume B - TeX: The Program 1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Volume D - METAFONT: The Program 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Volume E - Computer Modern Typefaces 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Samples of repro copy for Concrete Mathematics (the first major use of the AMS Euler typeface; 1988 sheets on Autologic 720dpi; 1990 on Linotron 1270dpi) 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous publications of the TeX Users Group: (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Membership list, September 26, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)